Derick Maitland Nieto

San José, Costa Rica 1148-6664

derickmaitland@gmail.com 💌

derickmaitland88 in

Jr Web Developer.

I have more than 15 years of experience working in sectors related to customer service, cashiers, sales, and cooking, I am always looking to learn new skills, take on additional responsibilities and grow professionally. I am currently in the process of learning new skills in programming to be a Web developer.

Experience

DECEMBER 2022 - CURRENTLY (PART-TIME)

Monitoring Operator / Johnson Controls

- Process monitoring signals entering the plant.
- Support additional tasks (projects) that the supervisor assigns, such as creating reports in Excel or analyzing information about the signals received.

SEPTEMBER 2016 - OCTOBER 2022

Support and Training Executive / Grupo Argus, Costa Rica

- Customer service via telephone, mail or face-to-face visits to the customer evacuating any doubt about the
 electronic billing systems acquired by the businesses.
- It helps to create reports for control of training to personnel and companies and internal audits.
- Assistance in developing web solutions for the company's clients using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

AUGUST 2012 - OCTOBER 2014

Administrative Assistant / Taco Bell, Costa Rica

- Perform administrative functions of personnel management, raw material inventories, waste control, during my shifts I earn two quality evaluations carried out by international audit of the company.
- In charge of training the new staff of the premises according to the need.
- Depending on the influx of customers, it relied on the customer service area.

Education

CURRENT

Bachelor degree in software engineering / Cenfotec University

Start of career in 2022 – 5% approved.

AUGUST 2006

Bachelor in Secondary Education / Liceo de Costa Rica

Skills and Languages

Spanish: Native

 English: B1 Conversational, B2 Reading and Listening Comprehension

Portuguese: B1 general

Excel: 80%

• Word: 80%

• Power BI: 80%

• SQL: 70%

Python: 60%

JavaScript: 55%

HTML – CSS: 65%

• Git: 65%